turn on tap
turn on oven
wash hands
pour soap
turn off tap
dry hands
open fridge
grab salmon
close fridge
put salmon
open cupboard
grab baking tray
close cupboard
put baking tray
open drawer
grab foil
close drawer
Open salmon
Pick up foil
Cut foil
Place foil
Open drawer
Close drawer
Get scissors
Cut foil in half
Put scissors in drawer
Close drawer
Pick up salmon
Put salmon on foil
put packaging on side
turn on tap
wash hands
turn off tap
grab oil
pour oil
close oil
put oil on side
grab pepper
open pepper
grind pepper
close pepper
put pepper on side
grab herbs
pour herbs
Pour herbs
Close herbs
Put herbs on side
Open fridge
Grab garlic paste
Close fridge
Press garlic paste
Get spoon
Open garlic paste
Squeeze garlic paste
scoop garlic paste
close garlic paste
open fridge
put garlic paste
close fridge
spread garlic
put spoon
grab Tabasco
open Tabasco
pour Tabasco
close Tabasco
put Tabasco on the side
grab salt
open salt
pour salt
sprinkle salt
dry hands
grab salt
put salt
wrap foil
put foil on tray
fold foil
grab foil
open drawer
put foil
close drawer
pickup kettle
fill kettle
close kettle
put kettle
turn kettle on
grab sauce pan
put sauce pan
open fridge
open drawer
grab potatoes
close drawer
close fridge
pour potatoes
Open fridge
Open drawer
Put potatoes
Close drawer
Close fridge
Grab salt
Open salt
Pour salt
Put salt
Turn on hob
Shake saucepan
Check temperature
Move saucepan
Grab kettle
Pour kettle
Put kettle
Grab tray
Open oven
Put tray in oven
Close the oven
[END SUBTITLE]